# **MAULANA YUSUF**

Perumnas cijerah blok.18 No.92, Bandung +62895704280433 maulana.vv@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Hi Im Maulana but you can call me Maul, I've been backend developer for about 6 years, and I like to learn and also discuss new things, especially technology industry. I'm develops web applications across third-party integrations and databases. Customizes interfaces to factor in unique demands for accessibility and security. Deeply familiar with coding languages and APIs.

#### Skills

- Problem-solving
- Code debugging
- Go
- SCALA
- GIT
- Vue

- Teamwork
- Quick learn somethink new
- NodeJs
- Sql / Nosql
- Laravel
- Reactjs

### **Experience**

Backend Developer

Aug 2018 - Nov 2022

#### Paxel

- · Wrote clean code to develop functional web applications.
- Resolved technical issues through debugging and research.
- Develop & maintenance API and internal dashboard Paxel.
- Provided third parties to integrate with open API

Backend Developer

Jun 2016 - Sep 2019

Relawan IT SSG Daarut Tauhid

- Collaborated with front-end developers to integrate web applications.
- · Handling bug or create new feature for user needs.

Data Engineering

Mar 2016 - Jul 2018

Nolimit

- · Resolved technical issues through debugging and research.
- · Create scrapping tools for collecting data from social media & online media
- Develop and maintenance API

#### Education

Barchelor Software Engineering Universitas Komputer Indonesia

Mar 2016

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak SMKN 11 Bandung

May 2011